[{"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "So it's quite a messy situation, isn't it?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Yes, that's right.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Could you explain what that means?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "THE TRIALS OF AMANDA KNOX\": Well, I don't know that there's been a lot of celebrification going on as much as demonization.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Are you concerned about the kind of celebrification of her through this case and the kind of pressure that will now put on her when she tries to return to normal life?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Well, it's been incredibly difficult, Piers.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "How have they all been bearing up?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Do you believe that she was guilty of lying?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "I can't speak for the family.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Thomas, I mean, do you believe the family feel so angry about the defamation conviction that they may seek to have that overturned?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, my overall take was there was nothing that I could glean from this young lady's history that suggested anything like the way she was portrayed in the Italian press or by the -- by the prosecutors in this case.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "What was your overall take of the whole thing?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "There's two things I want to comment on that, Piers.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "But from your assessment what kind of woman is Amanda Knox?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, Michael is no longer with us, obviously.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What is your primary motivation in going public now?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Did you find that with him?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Yes, Michael had great instincts, particularly with regard to marketing and promotion.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Like a good businessman, would you say?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Well, Michael was the genius.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "He must have thought you were a genius, didn't he?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "But in terms of the Beatles music, is that still part of Michael's estate?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Well, we bought the catalog in 1985.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "And in terms of the sheer number crunching here, could you tell me now what he paid for it and what it might now be worth?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "So he took it from 40-odd million to $1 billion?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, my co-executor John MaClean and I -- let's face it, Piers, we're fortunate to represent Michael Jackson.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What kind of decisions have you taken which have turned out to be very smart ones in relation to handling his estate?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "I'm not sure if that's true or not.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "It wasn't a long meeting.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "How did he seem to you?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Michael truly was one of a kind.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "In all your experience of working in the entertainment industry, how did Michael's business empire rank?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Well, that was an area that was handled by Michael's business managers and accountants.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "But was his spending out of control, as people kept saying it was?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Well, it's hard to compare.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "How do their estates compare in terms of how you manage them?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we've tried to do the right things.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "How fast have those assets appreciated since his death?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Am I right in thinking the estate is already petitioned to distribute 30 million dollars to the will's beneficiaries, who would be his immediate family and children?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Yes, I did, to Mrs. Jackson and several of Michael's siblings.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "John, presumably as the co-executor, would you have read the will to the family?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Very emotional.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "How was that?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Were you aware that that 2002 will was still in play?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I would think so.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Are they in a more relaxed frame of mind about it?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "That's true, Piers.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "There will be another show that's created permanently and specifically for a theater in Las Vegas in 2013.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "In 2013, it goes to Vegas permanently and there will be a Michael Jackson Museum?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "The issue in this case will be, did Conrad Murray engage in the appropriate standard of care for a physician in that situation.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "What do you make of all this?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I think the pressures of any allegations, even though they're false and even though it turns out you're acquitted, put tremendous pressure on you.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I think it was unparalleled.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "What did you think of his status as a performer?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "As Berry Gordy said, the greatest performer who ever lived.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "What do you think his legacy will be?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "For me, when people ask me to describe Michael Jackson, I say push the play button on the video or on your iPod and that says it all.", "docId": "111003pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Howard?", "qSentId": 533}]